One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
Rikkaus, maine, valta...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
"Merirosvokuningas" Gold Roger saavutti ne kaikki.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
Hänen viimeiset sanansa ajoivat valtavan määrän ihmisiä merille.
You want my treasure?
Aarteeniko?
Go ahead.
Sen kun otatte.
Find it!
Sopii etsiä!
Everything is right where I left it!
Siinä on koko maailman rikkaudet.
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
Ihmiset suuntasivat kohti Grand Linea unelmiensa perässä.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
Se oli alku merirosvojen ajalle!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Koko meren unelmat yhteen kerätään!
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for
Mitä sä tahotkaan löytää, mennään me etsimään!
One Piece!
One Piece!
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind
Kompassi turhaan matkaa hidastaa
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide
Kun ruoriin tartutaan, sydän ohjata saa!
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals
Ja pölynpeittämät vanhat aarrekartatkin
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real
just sykähdyttää siks ku ne on täynnä mysteerii!
When the world's got you down,
Elämä sinutkin
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
joskus vie myrskytuuliin
Their biorhythm will carry you through
Silloin ystävän selkään nojaa
We're gonna make the most of it
Sua kyllä tuetaan!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Koko meren unelmat yhteen kerätään!
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for
Mitä sä tahotkaan löytää, mennään me etsimään!
Got some change to my name,
Kolikko taskussain,
and maybe you wanna be my friend?
ja hei you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise!
We are, we are on the cruise!
WE ARE!
WE ARE!
The Second
Toinen
Is his arm okay?
Käsi on ehjä!
If he had backed off even one step, he would've lost it!
Jos hän olisi kiskonut, hampaat olisivat repineet sen.
I highly doubt he thought about how shark fangs work.
Tuskinpa tuo niin pitkälle hain hampaita ajatteli...
Is Big Bro's arm okay?
Onko Isoveljen käsi kunnossa?
H-Huh?
O-Oho?
Where'd he go?
Minne se meni?
Luffy! The sea!
Luffy! Meressä!
The sea?
Meressä?
There's a shark!
Siellä on hai!
That's Arlong!
Arlong se on!
What? Did he dive down?
Häh? Se sukelsi.
This is bad! He's even more powerful in the water!
Ei hyvä! Vedessä hänen voimansa kasvaa entisestään!
No one can stop me once I pick up speed underwater.
Vedessä pääsen pysäyttämättömään vauhtiin...!
This is a prime example of the kind of power only fishmen are blessed with.
Tällainen voima on siunattu vain meille merenmiehille!
Did he run away?
Karkasiko se?
Shark Gone...
Hai...
Darts!
Tikka!
What was that?!
Mitäh?!
A torpedo?!
Torpedoko se oli?!
Something flew out of the water!
Jotain syöksyi merestä!
Ow...! Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ai...! Ai, ai ai ai...
I'm impressed you dodged that.
Hyvin väistetty.
But the more you dodge, the longer you'll spend in hell.
Mutta mitä enemmän väistelet, sitä kauemmin piinasi jatkuu!
Shark Gone Darts!
Haitikka!
Wh-What the hell are that damn shark's bones made of?!
M-Millainen luusto tuolla hainkummajaisella on?!
His nose shattered the ground!
Tyyppi iski nenänsä kiven sisään...!
Shark Gone Darts!
Haitikka!
Hey Luffy, you gotta hide! He went into the water again!
Piiloudu, Luffy! Arlong pulahti taas veteen!
Big Bro! Hurry up and hide already!
Äkkiä piiloon, Isoveli!
He's gonna come after you again!
Hän tulee taas perääsi!
Get out of there!
Häivy jo!
N... No...
E... Ei käy...
Don't be stupid! You're a sitting duck right now! Take cover!
Älä typerehdi! Olet maalitauluna, suojaudu!
No way! I'll catch him and break his damn nose!
Ei käy! Otan sen kiinni ja väännän nenun poikki!
Come at me, shark!
Anti tulla, haikala!
You've got some nerve.
Pelkuri et ole.
Or perhaps you've realized that running away won't save you?
Vai tajusitko vain ettei hyödytä paeta?
What part of "hurry up and hide" don't you understand?!
Kätkeydy jonnekin, tahvo! Etkö tajua, Luffy?!
You couldn't even fully dodge any of his attacks!
Otat vain osumaa yhä uudestaan!
You'll die instantly if he hits you head-on!
Yksikin kunnollinen ja olet vainaa!
Gum-Gum...
Gumigumi...
Shield!
Kilpi!
What's with that stance?
Mikä tuo asento...?
He's not doing that to block it, is he?
Tuollako hän sen pysäyttää?!
I have twice the room to pick up speed now!
Vauhtia tuplasti pidemmältä!
I'll pierce right through your heart!
Sydämesi on pian vartaassa!
Shark Gone Darts!
Haitikka!
It's a direct hit!
Suora osuma!
Wait, did he get hit?!
Mitä nyt?! Osuiko se?!
No! He flung himself away!
Ei! Jätkä lennätti itsensä sivuun.
You lose! That attack won't work anymore!
Se oli siinä! Tuo temppu ei tepsi enää!
Shark Gone Darts!
Haitikka!
You bastard! That was just a lucky guess!
Kutale...! Se oli tuuria, eikö vaan?!
This is the final blow!
Armonisku!
Like that's gonna work!
Älä luule!
Gum-Gum...
Gumigumi...
Net!
Verkko!
Fishing! I'm fishing!
Anna Antti ahvenia!
And...
Ja...
Spear!
Keihäs!
Holy crap!
Jummijammi!
Alright, let's go!
Tuo tuntui!
Hm? Is he dead?
Hä? Kuoliko se?
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
Arlongin katse muuttui!
He looks just like the sea kings when they're pissed off.
Sama tuijotus kuin raivostuneilla merihirviöillä.
Luffy's last attack must've made him snap!
Äskeinen sai Arlongin veren kiehumaan...!
I've never seen Arlong look like that...
En ole koskaan nähnyt häntä tuon näköisenä...
Inferior human!
Alhainen ihmisolio!
Who do you think you are...
Mitä luulet tekeväsi...
to raise a hand against a fishman!?
merenmiehelle?!
Boy, that caught me by surprise!
Osasipa säikäyttää...
It didn't hurt, but he's definitely pissed.
Ei tosin sattunut. Taisi kaveri suuttua...
What the heck is that?
Mikä hitsi toi on?
The Shark Saw!
"Hammasrauta"!
That's a big-ass saw!
Megakokoinen saha!
Big Bro Luffy!
Isoveli Luffy!
Hang in there, Luffy!
Sinnittele, Luffy!
He just won't let up! Luffy is gonna get cornered! Run! Watch out!
Ei edes hengähdystaukoa! Hänet ajetaan nurkkaan! Juokse! Varo!
He escaped into the building!
Hän väisti sisälle!
The left window on the top floor...
Yläkerroksen vasen ikkuna...
That's the room where...
Tuo huonehan on...
There's nowhere left to run.
Pakomatka päättyi tähän.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
Tämä on Arlong Parkin ylin kerros.
What is this room?
Mikäs kumman huone?
It's full of papers.
Pelkkiä papereita.
They're no ordinary papers.
Ei mitä tahansa paperia.
This room is where I make that girl draw sea charts. This is...
Tänne Nami on pistetty piirtämään merikarttoja. Tämä on...
...the cartography room!
...karttahuone...!
Nami's room...
Namin huone...
Nami drew every one of these sea charts.
Nämä ovat kaikki hänen piirtämiä.
How many people in the world do you think can draw charts this accurate?
Kuinka moni muu tässä maailmassa osaisikaan piirtää näin tarkkoja karttoja?
That girl has a gift.
Se nainen on nero.
There's nothing as sad and senseless
Lahjojen hukkaan valuminen
as letting natural-born talent go to waste.
on surkuteltavin kohtalo!
She'll find true happiness by staying here and drawing charts!
Nami on siis onnellinen saadessaan piirtää karttoja täällä!
This pen is stained with blood...
Tähän kynään on pinttynyt verta...
These charts are absolutely vital if I am to achieve world domination!
Namin kartat ovat elintärkeitä maailman valloittamiseen!
That girl is going to keep drawing sea charts, for the sake of my ambition!
Se nainen tulee jatkamaan merikarttojen kyhäämistä mun tavoitteeni vuoksi!
Once we've learned everything about the world's seas from those charts,
Maailman meret kartoitettuamme
we fishmen will reign supreme, and my empire will span the globe!
me merenmiehet olemme voittamattomia, ja musta tulee maailmanvaltias!
This island and the East Blue are stepping stones toward that end!
Tämä saari ja East Blue ovat ponnahduslautani!
How could you possibly use her as effectively as me?!
Luuletko pystyväsi käyttämään sitä naista mua paremmin?!
What the...?! My Shark Saw...
Mitäh...?! Hammasrauta...
isn't budging!
ei hievahdakaan!
What?!
Mitä?!
"Use"?!
"Käyttää"?!
What's goin' on in there?!
Mitä sisällä on meneillään?!
Dammit... What happened, Big Bro Luffy?!
Saakura...! Miten Isoveli Luffy pärjää?
I can't tell what's going on up there at all...
Tänne alas ei näy yhtään mitään...
Luffy...
Luffy...
What do you take her for?!
Minä sä oikein pidät Namia?!
She may be an inferior creature, but she's a clever girl, too.
Hän on älykäs, vaikka onkin alempaa rotua...
If all other humans are sewer rats,
Jos muut ihmiset ovat rottia,
then she's a sassy little cat.
Nami voisi olla röyhkeä katinretale...
After all, she is adorable.
Herttainen otus silti.
I'm going to keep on feeding her and buying her the clothes she likes.
Ruokimme häntä, ostamme hienoja vaatteita...
She'll have everything she needs to live.
Häneltä ei puutu mitään!
All she has to do is keep drawing charts for me.
Hänen tarvitsee vain tehdä karttoja mulle.
She will forever be my tool...
Hän on näet työkaluni...
No...
Ei...
one of us.
vaan kumppanini.
What's that?!
Mitä nyt?!
A desk...?
Pöytä...?
It's a desk!
Pöytä vain...
Wh-Whew! It's just a desk.
N-Niinkö... Pelkkä pöytä...
Man, that scared me. I thought it was Big Bro Luffy for sure...
Huh sentään! Luulin että Isoveli Luffy...
Hold on, partner!
Kuules kamu!
Are you sayin' you don't have faith in Big Bro Luffy's strength?!
Etkö luota Isoveli Luffyn voimaan?!
Wha...?! You were scared too, Johnny!
Täh?! Itsekin säikyit, Johnny!
D-Don't be stupid! I was, uh, you know...
Tyhmäkö olet?! Mä, eh...
Obviously...
Tietysti...
Obviously I thought it was Arlong!
Luulin Arlongiksi, tietysti...
Huh?! It sounds like you're trying to pull one over on me!
Täh?! Kuulostaa siltä että koitat vedättää mua!
What's that, you jerk?! Obviously Big Bro Luffy would never lose!
Että mitä?! Isoveli Luffy ei tietenkään koskaan häviäisi!
Luffy?
Luffy?
What do you think you're doing?!
Mitä sä kuvittelet tekeväsi?!
What the hell is going on?! Stuff is flying everywhere!
Mitä ihmettä...?! Sieltä lentää kamaa ihan solkenaan!
Alright! As of today, this is your room!
Tämä on tästedes sun huoneesi.
Your desk, your pens...
Sun pöytäsi, sun kynäsi...
Everything you'll need is here!
Täällä on kaikki tarvittava!
Stop that!
Nyt saa riittää!
The charts!
Merikartat!
M-My charts!
M-Mun karttani!
You damn brat!
Senkin kakara!
Don't think you can trick me...
Turha yrittää petkuttaa...
drawing fake charts like that!
Ei enää valekarttoja!
Do you have the time to be drawing crap like this in secret?
Miten sinulla on aikaa piirrellä tällaista sontaa salassa?
Pull another stunt like that, and I'll drag the villagers here one by one
Jos vielä kerran teet samanlaisen tempun, raahaan kyläläiset tänne yksitellen...
and make you watch as I snuff out their lives!
ja pistän sut katsomaan kun päätän heidän päivänsä!
They'll meet the same fate she did!
Hänen laillaan!
Damn you! I spent eight years making her draw those!
Teetin noita Namilla vuosia!
I invested eight years in those charts! In my ambition!
Kulutin kahdeksan vuotta niihin karttoihin! Mun tavoitteeseeni!
Bell-mère...
Bell-mère...
Nojiko...!
Nojiko...!
This is a pretty intense fight!
Tämä vasta on raju matsi...
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
Joo! Kuolemaan asti.
Definitely!
Epäilemättä!
Thank you...!
Kiitos...
You've gone too far, you rubber freak!
Menit liian pitkälle, kumiretku!
"Fishmen are great"...
Vähät merenmiehistä...
"sea charts" this,
vähät kartoista...
"circumstances" that...
ja muista höpinöistä...
I don't know much about any of that stuff...
En tajua juttujasi eikä kiinnostakaan...
but I finally figured out how to save her!
mutta tiedän nyt, miten auttaa Namia...!
This room is why she can't leave this place!
Tällaista huonetta ei saisi olla olemassa!
It's not a home, it's a prison cell!
Nami ei tarvitse paikkaa, jossa hän ei edes tahdo olla!
I'm gonna tear this place to the ground!
Hajotan sen maan tasalle!
Gum-Gum...
Gumigumi...
Don't get cocky!
Älä luule liikoja!
Scum like you could never bring down Arlong Park!
Kaltaisesi mitätön itikka ei ikimaailmassa tuhoa Arlong Parkia!
Shark...
Hammas...
Tooth Drill!
Pyörä!
...Battle Axe!
...Kirves!
L-Look at that impact! Arlong Park is gonna...!
K-Katsokaa! Äskeinen sai Arlong Parkin säröille!
No way! It's gonna collapse!
Ei voi olla! Se alkaa sortua!
This is bad! Everyone, get back!
Varokaa! Äkkiä kauemmas!
Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
Pian, Isosisko Nami!
But Luffy's still inside!
Luffy on vielä sisällä!
Big Sis!
Isosisko!
Luffy! What about Luffy?!
Luffy! Luffy on...!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Luffy...
Luffy...
Ow... Oww!
Au... Auh!
What's all this damn noise?
Karsee melske...
Luffy...
Luffy...
Arlong Park... collapsed!
Arlong Park... sortui...!
Big Bro...
Isoveli...
What the hell happened in there?
Mitä sisällä oikein tapahtui?!
Who won?!
Kumpi voitti?!
Given all this debris... Don't tell me it was...!
Tuollainen tuho... Ei kai vain...!
Luffy...
Luffy...
Luffy!
Luffy!
– Big Bro!
– Isoveli!
Is he okay?!
Pahassa kunnossa...
Nami!
Nami!
You're one of us!
Sä olet mun toverini!
Yeah!
Kyllä!
More feelings than I can hold but I can’t make you understand
Paisuvii tunteitani hillittyä en mä saa More feelings than I can hold but I can’t make you understand
Be that as it may, I just can’t bear to let go of your hand
Tuli mitä tuli, puristan kättäs vaan tiukempaa Be that as it may, I just can’t bear to let go of your hand
I’ve still gotta move, even if I’m alone I’ll walk along
Liikkeessä mun täytyy pysyy, vaikka yksin kulkisin I’ve still gotta move, even if I’m alone I’ll walk along
Just promise that you’ll still keep an eye on me when I am gone
Lupaathan et mua silmällä pidät vielä kaukaakin Just promise that you’ll still keep an eye on me when I am gone
As soon as I woke up, couldn’t get it off my mind
Aamunkoitost saakka ihmettelin itsekin As soon as I woke up, couldn’t get it off my mind
“Why the hell’s it so hot? I can hardly breathe!”
Miks näin kuuma on sydämeni “Why the hell’s it so hot? I can hardly breathe!”
It’s been quite a while, but those thoughts just won’t seem to let go
Milloin alkoikaan loputon jano mua vaivaamaan - It’s been quite a while, but those thoughts just won’t seem to let go
But hey, what do I know?
But hey, what do I know? seikkailunhimo!
Guess I want a taste of that thing people call a “runner’s high”
Tietää halusin, milt tuntuu olla vauhdin huumassa Guess I want a taste of that thing people call a “runner’s high”
Think I chased too hard, and ended up leaving myself behind
Kiihdytin lujaa, vanha itsein jopa jäi kauas taa Think I chased too hard, and ended up leaving myself behind
All I want’s a taste of a dream that a sentence can’t define
Jahtaan unelmaa, jota en sanoiksi voi pukea All I want’s a taste of a dream that a sentence can’t define
Stick right by my side, and I can run, run, run until I die
Rinnallain kun ootte, voin juosta vailla loppua Stick right by my side, and I can run, run, run until I die